Another thing we can do is paraphrasing, so if I click on the paraphraser tool, let's see what this one has.
So paraphrasing is basically rewriting a text right, but for the very purpose that we're looking for.
So we can paraphrase a text for standard mode, we can paraphrase it for fluency.
So it will improve the clarity of what we have written.
We can humanize it, so the humanizer thing, we just used it.
We can make it formal, so we can give it an informal text and it will convert it to a formal one.
We can convert it to the academic language, so we can change the literature and the language of a text and make it seem more academic, so we can paraphrase it like that.
We can make it simpler, we can make it more creative, we can expand the text, so it will increase the length.
We can shorten the text and we have also custom unique descriptions, so we can give it a description ourselves.
So as you see, it is for the premium mode.
And in the premium mode, we can give it a custom command about what to do without text, right?
So, it's basically that. We can use the power freezer as well.